Guide to the Ronald Magden Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Ronald Magden collection, approximately 1879-1988; 5185-001; 10.4 cubic feet 12 boxes
  - Teamster Records
    - Clippings
      - Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers of America, 1919-1939, Undated (Box-folder 7/23-25)
      - Seattle Union Record, 1972 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Washington Teamster, 1942, 1972-1979, 1988 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1892-1927, 1974, 1993, Undated (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1894-1994, Undated (Box-folder 7/29-36)
    - Clippings, 1898-1996 (Box-folder:oversize 9/24-27, 11/5-7, 12/4)
  - Seattle Teamsters
    - Chronologies, Undated (Box-folder 7/37-40)
    - Constitution Of The Team Drivers’ International Union Of America, 1899 (Box-folder:oversize 9/28)
    - General Correspondence Of Employer’s Association Of Washington, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 7/41)
    - Minutes Of WCLU, 1903 (Box-folder 7/42)
    - Writings, 1913, Undated (Box-folder 7/43)
    - Lists, 1900, 1988 (Box-folder:oversize 11/8)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, circa 1989 (Box-folder 7/44-51)
    - Map, 1888 (Box-folder:oversize 11/9)
    - Photographs (photocopies), 1913 (Box-folder 7/52)
    - Clippings
      - Seattle Union Record, 1915-1928 (Box-folder 7/53-54)
      - Seattle Times, 1901-1934 (Box-folder 7/55-60)
      - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 7/61)
      - re: David Beck, 1993 (Box-folder 7/62)
      - re: David Beck, 1993 (Box-folder:oversize 11/10)
    - Clippings, 1899-1918 (Box-folder:oversize 11/11)
  - Tacoma Teamsters
    - Constitution Of Teamster’s Retirees Association, Undated (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Chronologies
      - Local 313, 1984-1939, Undated (Box-folder 8/2-3)
      - Washington State Teamster Unions and WWII, Undated (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Bakery Drivers Local #567, Undated (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Tacoma Teamsters Miscellany, Undated
    - Minutes Of “TTC”, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Agreements, 1958 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Interview Transcripts
      - Black, Clyde, 1989 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Curran, Charles and Mary Louise, 1988 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Johnson, Leon C., 1989 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Vogel, Art, circa 1989 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Writings Of Others, Undated (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Ledger Index Pages, Undated (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Lists, Undated (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Photographs (one Print, Others Photocopies), 1908, 1928-1930, Undated (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Clippings
      - Tacoma Labor Advocate, 1917-1959 (Box-folder 8/16-18)
      - Tacoma Daily Ledger, 1932-1939 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Washington Teamster, 1941-1979 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Seattle Union Record, 1919-1925 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Clippings, 1935-1951 (Box-folder:oversize 11/13)
  - Spokane Teamsters
    - Chronologies, Undated (Box-folder 8/22)
    - General Correspondence Of Ronald Magden, 1989 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Membership Roster, circa 1989 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Writings Of Ronald Magden--History Of Inland Empire Teamster Unions, Undated (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Writings Of Others, Undated (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Writings Of Others, 1937, 1954, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 11/14)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, Undated (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Lists, 1989 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Directories, 1889-1905 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Miscellany, Undated (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Clippings
      - Spokane Spokesman Review, 1893-1919 (Box-folder 8/31-32)
      - Spokane Labor World, 1910-1947 (Box-folder 8/33-34)
      - Spokane Chronicle, 1890-1917 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - Washington Teamster, 1942-1977 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Miscellaneous, 1890-1923, 1944-1987 (Box-folder 8/37)
    - Clippings, 1911-1934, 1964 (Box-folder:oversize 11/15)
  - Western Washington Teamsters
    - Chronologies, Undated (Box-folder 8/38)
    - Notes, Undated (Box-folder 8/39)
    - Clippings
      - Everett Labor Journal, 1910-1937 (Box-folder 8/40)
      - Washington Teamster, 1953-1977 (Box-folder 8/41-42)
      - Tacoma Labor Advocate, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 8/43)
      - Spokane Labor World, 1946
  - Central Washington Teamsters, 1952-1969 (Box-folder 8/44)
  - Newspaper Unions Publishing Company
    - Organizational Features, 1952 (Box-folder 8/45)
    - Incoming Letters, 1952-1968, 1983-1986. (Box-folder 8/46)
    - General Correspondence (Box-folder 8/47)
      - re: Annual Shareholders Meeting, 1963, 1971-1984
    - Minutes, 1954-1955, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 8/48)
    - Minutes, 1956-1974 (Box-folder:oversize 12/5)
    - Financial Records, 1952-1986 (Box-folder 8/49-50)
    - Stock Certificates, Undated (Box-folder 8/51)
    - Agreements, 1952 (Box-folder 8/52)
    - Exemption Affidavit, 1953 (Box-folder 8/53)
    - Writings Of Others, Undated (Box-folder 8/54)
    - Subject Series (Box-folder 8/55)
      - Portland Reporter, 1961
  - Oversized Material (as Described Above), 1888-1996 (Box:oversize 9-12)
- Ronald Magden collection, Undated; 5185-002; 12.9 cubic feet 15 boxes
  Ronald Magden's labor history research files
  Donor: Ronald E. Magden, August 17, 2011.
  The second accession is divided into five series:
  Research Files
  American Legion Hall Post #2
  Longshore History
  Tacoma History
  Washington State Labor Documents
  The first series, Research Files, is arranged chronologically. The second series, American Legion Hall Post #2 is arranged by material type and then chronologically. The third series, Longshore History has a number of subseries. The first is a general subseries which includes categories such as: Constitutions, Contracts and Agreements, Convention Proceedings, International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU), Photographs, Publications, Safety, Strikes, Waterfront Employers' Association (WEA), and the Washington Legislative League (WLL). Most of the materials are arranged chronologically, by organization, or by material type and then chronologically. The other subseries under Longshore History are Bellingham, National Labor Relations Board, Port Angeles, Portland, Port Townsend, San Francisco, Seattle, Tacoma and Vancouver. Most the the materials are arranged chronologically or by creator or material type and then chronologically. The fourth series, Tacoma History is arranged chronologically. The fifth series, Washington State Labor Documents, is arranged by location and then chronologically.
  - Research Files
    - Writings of Others, 1896-1994 (Box-folder 1/1)
      ʺCentralia: Tragedy and Trialʺ by Ben Hur Lampman
      ʺHarry Bridges: The Rise and Fall of Radical Labor in the United Statesʺ by Charles P. Larrowe
      Pacific Maritime Association articles
      ʺThe General Strike in San Franciscoʺ by Richard T. La Piere
      ʺSan Francisco: Act Oneʺ by Robert Cantwell
      ʺThe Beloved Sinnerʺ by Agnes Repplier
      ʺAmerican Public Opinion Reflected in the Pollsʺ by Dorothy Borg
      ʺTacoma, the Manufacturing and Shipping Center of the Pacific Northwestʺ
      ʺHistory of Employers' Associations in the United Statesʺ by Clarence E. Bonnett
      ʺSeasonal Unemployment in Washington"
      "Building Bridges: Newsletter of the Center for Labor Studiesʺ
      ʺIn the Name of History: A Disciplinary Critique of Orlando Fals Borda's Historia doble de la costa'ʺ by Charles Bergquist
      ʺThe Birth of A State: The Journal of The Washington State Constitutional Convention 1889ʺ edited by Charles M Rosen, Beverly Paulik Gates
      ʺ1896 Record of American and Foreign Shippingʺ published by the American Shipmasters' Association
    - Papers, Notes, Clippings on Unions and Japanese, 1913-1999 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1934-2001 (Box-folder 1/3)
      National Negro Labor Council Statement: ʺBrownell Adds to Our Shameʺ
      Warning from Roger Ebert to Avoid Northwest Film Festival Showing of Karl Krogstad's film ʺSex with an Octopus"
      Brochures: The Harry Bridges Institutes Video History Project
      International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU) articles
      Stanford Law Review
      Ernie Tanner Scholarship Fund
    - Magden Notes, Clippings, Writings of Others, 1958-2005 (Box-folder 1/4)
      General Perspective and Program: ILWU Negotiating Committee
      Pacific Maritime Association Bulletin, 1958
      ʺThe Oxford Group and the Strike of the Seattle Longshoremen in 1934ʺ by Eckard V. Toy, 1978
      ʺChapter VII: Our Seattle Revolutionʺ from I Change Worlds: the Remaking of an American by Anna Louise Strong, 1937
      ʺEarly Washington State Labor Historyʺ by Stanley Nelson, 1938; ʺAnd the Challenges of Our Second Centuryʺ from United Mine Worker's Journal
      Longshore articles, 1990
      Tacoma's News Tribune, June 2005
      ʺReform Politics in Seattle During the Progressive Eraʺ by Mansel Blackford, 1968
      ʺLeftward Tilt on the Pacific Slope: Indigenous Unionism and the Struggle Against AFL Hegemony in the State of Washingtonʺ by Carlos Schwantes, 1979
      ʺA Tale of Two Ports;ʺ Seattle Times, 1995
    - Clippings: Non-Union, 1961-2000 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1962-1997 (Box-folder 1/6)
      Japanese History
      Seattle World’s Fair History
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1963-1998 (Box-folder 1/7)
      Business Cards
      Receipts
      Longshoremen: Clayton Jones Biography
    - Clippings: Unions (Non-Longshore), 1964-1998 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Manuscript, 1980 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1984-2003 (Box-folder 1/10)
      Longshore History Article: “Fifty years on the docks” by Magden
      Newspaper: Northwest Black Pioneers News
    - Notes, Correspondence: Post World War II Japanese History Project, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Notes: Longshore History, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/13)
      Northwest Trek Living History Project Script: "The Railroader"
      Longshore History Newsletter: “On the Waterfront”
      Port of Tacoma Program: 55th Anniversary of the 1934 Strike
    - Writings of Others, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 1/14)
      “Fink, the Labor Connection” by Archie Green
      “Popular Front Unionism in a Small Place: The Woodworkers of Pacific County, Washington, 1935-1941” by Jeremy R. Egolf
      “Waterfront Poems” by Alfredo Valenzuela
    - Correspondence: Harry Bridges Memorial Committee, 1992 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1992-2005 (Box-folder 1/16)
      “A History of Seattle Waterfront Workers” Publication
      Correspondence re: Publication of “Furusato”
      Pamphlets, Correspondence: Citizens for a Healthy Bay Harry Bridges
    - University of Washington Tacoma Student Questions on Longshoremen, 1998 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Book: Furusato: Tacoma Pierce County Japanese by Ronald Magden, 1998 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Miscellaneous Papers and Photographs, Undated (Box-folder 1/19)
      Tacoma Longshore Presentation Outline by Magden
      Photographs: Harry Bridges, Local 19
    - Biographical Notecards, Undated (Box-folder 1/20)
  - American Legion Hall Post #2
    - History Indexes
      - History Index (Part 1/2), 1947-1958 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - History Index (Part 2/2), 1956-1961 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Minutes
      - Minutes (Part 1/4), 1941-1947 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Minutes (Part 2/4), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Minutes (Part 3/4), 1960-1964 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Minutes (Part 4/4), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Longshore History
    - General
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1889-2005 (Box-folder 2/7)
        Graph: Historical Evolution of Major Tacoma Longshore Unions
        Member Records: Marine Cooks’ and Stewards’ Association of the Pacific Coast
        Minutes: Seattle Strike Committee, 1937
        Incoming Communications: Secretary of ILWU Sub-District Council of Puget Sound Area District 38, 1937
        Clippings
        1934 Strike
        Harry Bridges
        Stevedores
        ILWU Newspaper: The Hook
        Agenda: ILWU Clerk and Walking Boss Caucus, 2005
        Correspondence: Puget Sound Council Pacific Maritime Association
        ILA
        W.C. Dawson
        List: Longshore Leadership
        Script: “Mercer Girls” Radio Program, 1939
        Tacoma Cemetery Records
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1898-1998 (Box-folder 2/8)
        ʺThe Tacoma Waterfront;ʺ ʺLife and Work of the Tacoma Longshoremenʺ
        Tacoma Sunday Ledger, 1898
        Property Inventory Update
        Founders of ILWU Local 19
        ILWU Pensioners' Club
      - Writings of Others, 1906-1934 (Box-folder 2/9)
        “Wages and Hours of Labor,” Monthly Labor Review, 1921
        “Industrial Democracy: The Longshoremen’s Association,” by Luke Grant
        The Outlook, 1906
        “The Ship Must Sail on Time,” by Ernest Pool
        Everybody’s Magazine, 1908
        “The Longshoremen and the War,” by Ruth Pickering
        The Survey, 1916, 1917-1920
        “A Peculiar Eight Hour Problem,” by William Z. Ripley
        Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1919
        “Peace along Shore: How the Longshoremen Settle Difference with Employers,” by B.M. Squires
        The Survey, 1920
        “Longshore,” by William Z. Ripley, The Survey, 1922
        “Five Men on a Dead Man’s Chest, Yo, Ho!” by Robert W. Bruère, The Survey, 1922
        “Dockwallopers,” by Paul Peters, The American Mercury, 1930
        “Harbor-Workers,” by Lewis W. Hine
      - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA) and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU) Papers: Correspondence, Bulletins, Donation List, 1907-1938 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - ILA and ILWU Charters OVERSIZE, 1908-1953 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Reports: Wage Scales and Working Conditions, 1918-1932 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Articles and Reports: Working Conditions, 1921-1967 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Ledger, 1930 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - ILA and ILWU Papers: Minutes, Arbitrations, Petitioner’s Exhibits, 1934-1940 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Correspondence: Arbitrator’s Award, 1935 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Bulletins: “Daily Radio News,” “The Northern Line”, 1938 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Membership Cards, 1943-1949 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Memorandum of Understanding: Pacific Maritime Association and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1958-1998 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Correspondence, Articles: Maritime Workers Historical Association, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1982-2004 (Box-folder 2/20)
        Letters
        Newspaper: The Dispatcher, 2004
        Labor Songs
        Newsletter: UW Center for Labor Studies,1999
        Visitor's Guide: Port of Tacoma
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1987-2002 (Box-folder 2/21)
        Magazine: Marine Digest, 1987
        Brochure: “Fred Zinn: Artist of the Working Waterfront,”1992
        Ephemera: “The Working Longshoremen, Tacoma Seafood Extravaganza,” 1991
        Conference Schedule: UW Center for Labor Studies
        “Workers in the Global Economy: Organizing for a New Century,” 1995
        Newspaper Article: CIO
        “Bibliography: Seattle General Strike”
        Report: “International Longshore and Warehouse Union Longshore, Clerk and Walking Boss Caucus,” 2002
      - Working Papers: Harry Bridges Center for Labor Studies Student, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Pacific Maritime Association (PMA) Annual Report, 1995 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Books, Brochures, Pamphlets
        - United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics Bulletin No. 550 "Cargo Handling and Longshore Labor Conditions", 1932 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934, Arbitration Before National Longshoremen's Board, Oral Argmnt of Herman Phleger, Esq. on behalf of Waterfront Employers", 1935 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Maritime Labor Board, Report to the President and to the Congress”, 1940 (Box-folder 3)
        - "First Report Un-American Activities in Washington State" by the Joint Legislative Fact-Finding Committee on Un-American Activities, 1948 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Report From Europe, By the Rank and File Delegation of the International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, With Foreword By Harry Bridges", 1949 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Maritime Association (PMA): Supercargo List-Washington Area, 1974 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Time Book, 2000 (Box-folder 3)
      - Constitutions
        - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Constitution, 1928 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Local 13 Constitution, 1948 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1961 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1965 (Box-folder 3)
        - Marine Clerks Association, Local 63, International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Constitution, Appendix, and Rules of Order", 1965 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1967 (Box-folder 3)
        - International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union Local 52 Constitution, Port Supplement and Working Rules of the Checkers, Supercargoes, and Supervisors Association of the State of Washington, 1967 (Box-folder 3)
        - Marine Clerks Association, Local 63, International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Constitution and Rules of Order, 1974 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU (2 copies), 1975 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1977 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1979 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Local 142 Constitution, 1979 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution (2 copies), 1981 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution (3 copies), 1988 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution (5 copies), 1991 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution (3 copies), 1994 (Box-folder 3)
        - ILWU Constitution, 1997 (Box-folder 3)
      - Contracts and Agreements
        - "Agreement Between Pacific Coast Longshore Division ILWU and Waterfront Employers of the Pacific Coast on behalf of Waterfront Employers of Washington, Waterfront Employers of Portland, Waterfront Employers Association of San Francisco, Waterfront Employers Association of Southern California", 1938 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Pacific Longshore Agreement: With Working and Dispatching Rules for the Ports of the Colombia River and Portland and Vancouver Dock Agreement", 1948-1951 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Agreements Covering: Longshoremen and Dock Workers in the Ports of Tacoma, Port Angeles and Anacortes (10/1/54), Checkers and Supervisors in the Port of Tacoma (10/1/54), I.B.L. Foremen (6/25/56), 1956 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Agreement, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 3)
        - "Container Freight Station Supplement to the Pacific Coast Longshore and Clerks' Agreement" Between ILWU and Pacific Maritime Association, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (2 copies), 1966-1971 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3)
        - All Alaska Longshore Agreement, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (2 copies), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (3 copies), 1984-1987 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Clerks’ Contract Document, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Walking Bosses & Foremen’s Agreement, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (3 copies), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 3)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (6 copies), 1990-1993 (Box-folder 4)
        - Pacific Coast Clerks’ Contract Document, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (3 copies), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4)
        - Pacific Coast Walking Bosses & Foremen’s Agreement, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (3 copies), 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4)
        - Pacific Coast Longshore Contract Document (3 copies), 1999-2002 (Box-folder 4)
      - Convention Proceedings
        - ILA and ILWU Convention Proceedings OVERSIZE, 1899-1929 (Box-folder 13/2)
        - ILA and ILWU Convention Proceedings OVERSIZE, 1934-1967 (Box-folder 13/3)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings (Copy 1), 1935 (Box-folder 5/1)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings (Copy 2), 1935 (Box-folder 5/2)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings (Copy 1), 1936 (Box-folder 5/3)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings (Copy 2), 1936 (Box-folder 5/4)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings (3 copies), 1937 (Box-folder 4)
        - ILA: Pacific Coast District Convention Proceedings, 1939 (Box-folder 5/5)
        - ILWU Convention Proceedings (2 copies), 1938 (Box-folder 4)
        - ILWU Convention Proceedings, 1976 (Box-folder 5/6)
        - ILWU Convention Proceedings, 1983 (Box-folder 5/7)
        - Maritime Federation of the Pacific Coast Convention Proceedings (Copy 1), 1936 (Box-folder 5/8)
        - Maritime Federation of the Pacific Coast Convention Proceedings (Copy 2), 1936 (Box-folder 5/9)
        - Maritime Federation of the Pacific Coast Convention Proceedings, 1939 (Box-folder 4)
        - Washington State Industrial Union Council, Council of Industrial Organizations (CIO) Convention Proceedings, 1948 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA)
        - Roster: Officers and Members, 1916 (Box-folder 5/11)
        - Correspondence, Proposals: Modification of Arbitrator’s Award, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Correspondence: Removal of Harry Bridges, 1936 (Box-folder 5/13)
        - Memorandum, Correspondence: Sailor’s Union and Scaler’s Union Settlement, 1936 (Box-folder 5/14)
        - Minutes: Pacific Coast District Executive Board, 1936 (Box-folder 5/15)
        - Minutes: Sub-District Council of Puget Sound Area, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - International Warehousemen's and Longshoremen's Union (ILWU)
        - Report: Unemployment Insurance, 1959 (Box-folder 5/17)
        - Miscellaneous Papers, 1965-1979 (Box-folder 5/18)
          International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Convention Proceedings
          Correspondence
          Trade Unions
          United Farm Workers
        - Minutes: Puget Sound District Council Meeting, 1991 (Box-folder 5/19)
        - Book: A History of the Federated Auxiliaries of the ILWU, 1934-1984 by Joan Fox, 1993 (Box-folder 5/20)
        - Directories, 1995-1997, 1999 (Box-folder 5/21)
        - Speech: Del Egbert at the Longshore Clerk and Walking Boss Caucus of the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1996 (Box-folder 6/1)
        - Coast Committee Reports: Contract Bargaining, 2003 (Box-folder 6/2)
        - Foriegn Policy
          - Vietnam, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 6/3)
          - Cambodia, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 6/4)
          - Chile, 1974-2005 (Box-folder 6/5)
          - South Africa, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 6/6)
          - El Salvador, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 6/7)
          - Korea and the Philippines, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 6/8)
            Kim Dae Jung
            Marcos Murders in Seattle
          - International Trade, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 6/9)
        - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union-Pacific Maritime Association (ILWU-PMA) Healthcare Pamphlets and Brochures
          - Death, Accidental Death and Accidental Dismemberment Benefit Programs, 1990 (Box-folder 7)
          - Death, Accidental Death and Accidental Dismemberment Benefit Programs, 1992 (Box-folder 7)